Its objective was to search for advanced extraterrestrial life.
The ship disappeared approximately 16 years into the mission.
And the commander was?
He was my father, sir.
This might come as quite a shock to you.
Your father was experimenting with a highly classified material.
God, it seems like a thousand years ago.
I fought my way out of that cave, became Iron Man,
realized I loved you.
And we're looking to be alive.
Whoa, whoa, stop, Don't come any closer.
It's a girl. Girl! Oh my gosh, girl.
I'm sorry. Don't move on here.
I've just never seen a girl before.
Who are you?
But a new day brings new opportunities
and i was ready to make a statement
how does the same go
i am what
did what i had to do
to protect our world
you can't control everything strange
You open the doorway between universes
and we don't know who or what will walk through it
Wanda,
Whatever's on you,
is on us.
He's got his own private army.
We need help.
No way.
So how do y'all want to play this?
Fast.
It's Mayan.
They made human sacrifices here.
It's somthing there.
Hey budd, had you ever thought there has got to be more?
More of what?
stuff we do day after day
Literally not once.
Today's gonna be different, Goldie.
What are we looking at?
Who are you?
We ran into each other the other day.
how did you found me?
I waited, outside by the murder train
He knew every move of mine before I made it
I have him right there, and take the shot.
And he'd be gone, like a ghost.
This is our only chance.
We have to take it
We need calm
is there another creature that might stand a chance against him
My god.
Scylla.
Our planet will perish.
M.I.B., you Karelian scum.
And FYI, your little club here sucks.
Come on.
The world's not going to save itself.
I'm driving.
That really should be here.
I love this country.
shall we?
I thought that we were here.
Otto, take the stone back to the lair.
I'll distract them.
I'll handle this.
It's not a birthmark, Cole.
It means you've been chosen.
Throughout history, different cultures all over the world
reference a great tournament
of champions.
That dragon marking?
I think it's an invitation
to fight for some...
Gotta kill the person you were born to be in order to become the person you want to be
I'm thinking of changing my name to Elton.
That's my name.
Yeah, I know
You can be the best-selling artist in america if you desire.
I was trying to do something bold
Hey mom
I didn't get a chance to walk her.
Bad dragon, back to your lair.
Come, dear brother, our destiny awaits.
Okay, I'm coming.
Wrong.
I'm in charge
allow me to clarify
In a sequentially ranked hierarchy based on level of critical importance the disparity between us is too vast to quantify
Agent Stone
the doctor thinks you're basic
listen pound.
I don't know if you realize
I'm sorry major.
What was your name?
Benny, nobody cares
In the neighborhood spider-man
Bitch, please you've been to space.
What do you want, Peter?
I want to go back on my trip with the girl who I really like and tell her how I feel.
MJ, I...
I am Spider-Man.
No, of course I'm not.
I mean, it's kind of obvious.
Does any part of you feel relieved about all this?
What do you mean?
Now that everybody knows, you don't really have to hide or lie to people.
For the record, I never wanted to lie to you.
And how do you tell someone that you're Spider-Man?
Now everybody knows.
But this isn't a...
A thousand generations live in you now.
But this is your fight.
BEGGING FOR SCRAPS
EVERYTHING YOU SEE
EXISTS TOGETHER IN A DELICATE BALANCE
Remember what I told you?
Do you ever feel lost?
Just look into the eyes of the people that you love.
Not me.
What?
Just listening.
May very well mean the difference between life
and death.
Your reputation precedes you.
I have to admit I wasn't expecting an invitation back.
Phoenix.
Hello, Jean.
Who are you?
The better question is,
who are you?
Something's happening to me.
When I lose control, bad things happen.
But it feels good.